<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<factory>
	<!-- Box -->
	<method name="createHorizontalBox">
		<description>Creates a Box that displays its components from left to right, using X_AXIS
		style.</description>
		<parameters>
			<parameter name="layout.has">true</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.name">horizontalBox</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.acronym">hbox</parameter>
		</parameters>
	</method>
	<method name="createVerticalBox">
		<description>Creates a Box that displays its components from top to bottom, using Y_AXIS
		style.</description>
		<parameters>
			<parameter name="layout.has">true</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.name">verticalBox</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.acronym">vbox</parameter>
		</parameters>
	</method>
	<!-- Glue -->
	<method name="createGlue">
		<description>Creates an invisible "glue" component that can be useful in a Box whose visible
			components have a maximum width (for a horizontal box) or height (for a vertical box). You can
			think of the glue component as being a gooey substance that expands as much as necessary to fill
			the space between its neighboring components.</description>
		<parameters>
			<parameter name="variable.name">glue</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.acronym">glue</parameter>
		</parameters>
	</method>
	<method name="createHorizontalGlue">
		<description>By putting horizontal glue between two components in a left-to-right box, you make any
			extra space go between those components, instead of to the right of all the components.
		</description>
		<parameters>
			<parameter name="variable.name">horizontalGlue</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.acronym">hglue</parameter>
		</parameters>
	</method>
	<method name="createVerticalGlue">
		<description>By putting vertical glue between two components in a top-to-bottom box, you make any
			extra space go between those components, instead of to the bottom of all the components.
		</description>
		<parameters>
			<parameter name="variable.name">verticalGlue</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.acronym">vglue</parameter>
		</parameters>
	</method>
	<!-- Strut -->
	<method name="createRigidArea">
		<parameter type="java.awt.Dimension" defaultSource="new java.awt.Dimension(20, 20)"/>
		<description>Use this rigid area you want a fixed-size space between two components. It is recommended
			to use rigid areas instead of struts.</description>
		<parameters>
			<parameter name="variable.name">rigidArea</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.acronym">rgd</parameter>
		</parameters>
	</method>
	<method name="createHorizontalStrut">
		<parameter type="int" defaultSource="20"/>
		<description>Creates an invisible, fixed-width component. In a horizontal box, you typically use this
			method to force a certain amount of space between two components. In a vertical box, you might use
			this method to force the box to be at least the specified width. The invisible component has no
			height unless excess space is available, in which case it takes its share of available space, just
			like any other component that has no maximum height.</description>
		<parameters>
			<parameter name="variable.name">horizontalStrut</parameter>
			<parameter name="variable.acronym">hstrut</parameter>
		</parameters>
	</method>
	<method name="createVerticalStrut">
		<parameter type="int" defaultSource="20"/>
		<description>Creates an invisible, fixed-height component. In a vertical box, you typically use this
			method to force a certain amount of space between two components. In a horizontal box, you might
			use this method to force the box to be at least the specified height. The invisible component has
			no width unless excess space is available, in which case it takes its share of available space,
			just like any other component that has no maximum width.</description>
	<parameters>
		<parameter name="variable.name">verticalStrut</parameter>
		<parameter name="variable.acronym">vstrut</parameter>
	</parameters>
	</method>
</factory>
